# Dmitri Stefanisin



# CONTACT

312-513-3256 email.ds@protonmail.com Oak Park / Chicago, IL LinkedIn.com/in/dmitri-stefanisin GitHub/imdmitri1

# **ABOUT ME**

I came to the U.S. from Moldova six years ago to live and work in a country full of opportunities to advance professionally. My natural curiosity entices me to learn and figure out how things work which led me to discover the power of web development. I'm looking to join a development team that is solving complex user experience challenges through code.

# **SKILLS**

Proficient: Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, RSpec JavaScript, jQuery, Jasmine, SQLite, Heroku Active Record, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Git Exposure: React, React Native, AWS, AngularJS

# **EDUCATION**

#### **DEV BOOTCAMP**

Full-Stack Web Development (2017)

## ACADEMY OF ECONOMIC STUDIES OF MOLDOVA

Corporate Finance and Insurance (2010 – 2011)
Bachelor in Business Administration (2006 – 2010)

## LANGUAGES

English, Russian, Ukrainian, Romanian

## INTERESTS

Living a healthy lifestyle, travel, motorcycles

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **DEV BOOTCAMP**

APR 2017 - OCT 2017

Student (Chicago, IL)

- Programming skills (front-end & back-end)
- Engineer Empathy (team dynamics, microaggressions)
- Pair programming (feedback)
- Test Driven Development & Agile workflow

### SDV CO

MAY 2012 - FEB 2017

Long-Distance Driver / Self-Employed (Chicago, IL)

- Coordinated cargo loads with company brokers and shipping/receiving personnel at pick-up and delivery destinations through contiguous United States (including cargo at borders and ports)
- Maintained detailed business records
- Responsible for safety and integrity of all cargo loads

#### **SEWARD FISHERY**

JUN 2011 - SEP 2011

Quality Assurance Supervisor (Seward, Alaska)

- Responsible for determining quality of fish received at docks in order to ensure freshness prior to processing (average volume of 500,000 pounds/day)
- Handled and processed documentation associated with incoming shipments of fish
- Interacted directly with all fishermen and employees on the docks

# **PORTFOLIO**

Conversation Partner (helps new English learners to practice their communication skills)

DBCStackOverflow (popular Stack Overflow website clone built with Sinatra)